Jean MOREL

Public Sector | Reserved Military Nurse Applicant

jeanmorel@icloud.com | +262 693 97 07 84

97460 Saint-Paul, La Réunion

Born: December 9, 1978 - Le Port (97420), France

Licenses: B & C | French | Single

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/jean-morel-infirmier-de

Profile

Military Nurse in the French Military Health Service for the past 25 years, I have served in various military branches including the Navy, Army, Volunteer Firefighters, Gendarmerie, and Air and Space Force, both in units and in hospitals, in mainland France and overseas operations.

With this wide-ranging experience and specialized skills, and as a recognized disabled worker injured in the line of duty, I am deeply motivated to commit myself to healthcare in La Réunion. I am actively seeking a Reserved Military Job adapted to my condition, as a nurse in the French public sector in La Réunion.

Key Skills

- Emergency Nurse Coordinator (I.O.A.)
- Hyperbaric Care Nurse (I.T.S.H.)
- Hemovigilance Referent
- Collective Medical Air Evacuation (MORPHEE)

Languages

- French (including Réunion Creole)
- English Intermediate

Professional Experience

2024 - General Medicine - 72H, CHOR Hospital, Saint-Paul

2019-2020 - Specialized Surgery, CPEMPN & Pharmacy, Percy Military Hospital, Clamart

2017 - Personnel Medicine, Laveran Military Hospital, Marseille

2016-2017 - IT Security Officer (CORSIC), Medical Unit - Air Base 125, Istres

2013-2016 - Nurse, Gendarmerie Medical Unit, Sathonay-Camp

2008-2011 - Volunteer Firefighter Nurse (ISPV), SDIS 69 (SAMU 69), Saint-Priest

2005-2013 - Emergency Nurse Coordinator (I.O.A.), Desgenettes Military Hospital, Lyon

Jean MOREL

Education & Certifications

Dec. 2016 - Certified in Collective Air Medical Evacuation (MORPHEE), Air Base 125, Istres

Dec. 2015 - Hyperbaric Nurse Technician (I.T.S.H.), IMNSSA Naval Medical Center / Val-de-Grace, Toulon

Oct. 2008 - Emergency Nurse Organizer (I.O.A.), Desgenettes Military Hospital, Lyon

2007-2009 - Volunteer Firefighter Nurse (ISPV), SDIS 69, Lyon

2000-2003 - State Registered Nurse Diploma (DEI), EPPA Toulon / DRASS Marseille